A Guide to the Papers of Arthur W. Mitchell 1910-1950
Johnston Memorial Library, Virginia State University
- Congressional Correspondence
  - Congressional 1935-1942
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 april 11-20 (Box-folder 25:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 April 21-25 (Box-folder 25:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 april 26-30 (Box-folder 25:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 May 1-5 (Box-folder 25:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 May 6-10 (Box-folder 25:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 May 11-15 (Box-folder 25:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 May 16-19 (Box-folder 25:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 May 20-25 (Box-folder 25:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 May 26-31 (Box-folder 25:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 June 1-10 (Box-folder 25:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 June 11-19 (Box-folder 25:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 June 20-30 (Box-folder 25:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 July (Box-folder 26:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Aug (Box-folder 26:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 sept 1-15 (Box-folder 26:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Sept 16-23 (Box-folder 26:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Sept 24-31 (Box-folder 26:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Oct 1-10 (Box-folder 26:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Oct 11-20 (Box-folder 26:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Oct 21-31 (Box-folder 26:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Nov 1-10 (Box-folder 26:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Nov 11-19 (Box-folder 26:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Nov 20-21 (Box-folder 26:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Dec 1-10 (Box-folder 27:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Dec 11-20 (Box-folder 27:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Dec 21-31 (Box-folder 27:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Jan 1-5 (Box-folder 27:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Jan 6-10 (Box-folder 27:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Jan 11-14 (Box-folder 27:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Jan 16-19 (Box-folder 27:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Jan 20-25 (Box-folder 27:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1938 Jan 26-31 (Box-folder 27:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Feb 1-5 (Box-folder 27:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Feb 6-10 (Box-folder 27:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Feb 11-15 (Box-folder 27:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Feb 16-20 (Box-folder 28:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Feb 21-28 (Box-folder 28:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 mar 1-5 (Box-folder 28:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 mar 6-10 (Box-folder 28:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Mar 11-20 (Box-folder 28:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 mar 21-25 (Box-folder 28:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Mar 26-31 (Box-folder 28:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 April 1-5 (Box-folder 28:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 april 6-10 (Box-folder 28:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 april 11-13 (Box-folder 28:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 April 14-16 (Box-folder 28:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 April 17-19 (Box-folder 28:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 april 20-24 (Box-folder 28:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 April 25-30 (Box-folder 28:14)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 May 1-4 (Box-folder 29:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 May 5-10 (Box-folder 29:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 may 11-15 (Box-folder 29:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 may 16-20 (Box-folder 29:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 may 31-27 (Box-folder 29:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 May 28-31 (Box-folder 29:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 June 1-6 (Box-folder 29:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 June 7-10 (Box-folder 29:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 june 11-14 (Box-folder 29:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 June 15-19 (Box-folder 29:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 June 20-25 (Box-folder 29:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 June 26-30 (Box-folder 29:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 July 1-10 (Box-folder 29:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 July 13-20 (Box-folder 29:14)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 july 21-28 (Box-folder 29:15)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Aug (Box-folder 30:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Sept 1-19 (Box-folder 30:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Sept 20-25 (Box-folder 30:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Sept 26-30 (Box-folder 30:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Oct 1-10 (Box-folder 30:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Oct 11-19 (Box-folder 30:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Oct 20-31 (Box-folder 30:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Nov 1-10 (Box-folder 30:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Nov 11-31 (Box-folder 30:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Dec 1-10 (Box-folder 30:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Dec 11-19 (Box-folder 30:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1939 Dec 20-31 (Box-folder 30:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Jan 1-5 (Box-folder 31:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Jan 6-10 (Box-folder 31:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Jan 11-15 (Box-folder 31:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Jan 16-17 (Box-folder 31:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Jan 18-19 (Box-folder 31:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Jan 20-23 (Box-folder 31:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Jan 24-25 (Box-folder 31:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Jan 26-28 (Box-folder 31:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Jan 29-31 (Box-folder 31:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Feb 1-3 (Box-folder 31:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Feb 5 (Box-folder 31:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Feb 6-10 (Box-folder 31:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Feb 11-13 (Box-folder 32:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Feb 14-15 (Box-folder 32:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Feb 16-19 (Box-folder 32:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Feb 20-25 (Box-folder 32:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Feb 26 - 27 (Box-folder 32:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Feb 28-29 (Box-folder 32:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Mar 1-5 (Box-folder 32:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Mar 6-10 (Box-folder 32:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Mar 11-14 (Box-folder 32:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Mar 15-18 (Box-folder 32:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Mar 19-21 (Box-folder 32:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Mar 22-25 (Box-folder 32:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Mar 26-31 (Box-folder 32:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 April 1-5 (Box-folder 33:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 April 6-10 (Box-folder 33:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 April 11-15 (Box-folder 33:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 April 16-22 (Box-folder 33:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 April 23-25 (Box-folder 33:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 April 26-31 (Box-folder 33:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 May 1-5 (Box-folder 33:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 May 6-10 (Box-folder 33:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 May 11-17 (Box-folder 33:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 May 18-25 (Box-folder 33:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 May 26-31 (Box-folder 33:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 June 1-5 (Box-folder 33:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 June 6-10 (Box-folder 33:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 June 11-12 (Box-folder 33:14)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 June 13-15 (Box-folder 33:15)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 June 16-24 (Box-folder 33:16)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 June 25-31 (Box-folder 34:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 July 1-5 (Box-folder 34:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 July 6-11 (Box-folder 34:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 July 12-22 (Box-folder 34:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 July 23-31 (Box-folder 34:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Aug 1-5 (Box-folder 34:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Aug 6-10 (Box-folder 34:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Aug 12-19 (Box-folder 34:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Aug 20-24 (Box-folder 34:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Aug 26-31 (Box-folder 34:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Sept 2-10 (Box-folder 34:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Sept 11-19 (Box-folder 34:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Sept 20-31 (Box-folder 34:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Oct 1-5 (Box-folder 35:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Oct 6-10 (Box-folder 35:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Oct 11-14 (Box-folder 35:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Oct 15-23 (Box-folder 35:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Oct 24-30 (Box-folder 35:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Nov 1-10 (Box-folder 35:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Nov 11-15 (Box-folder 35:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Nov 16-19 (Box-folder 35:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Nov 20-31 (Box-folder 35:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Dec 1-8 (Box-folder 35:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Dec 9-10 (Box-folder 35:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Dec 11-15 (Box-folder 35:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1940 Dec 16-30 (Box-folder 35:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Jan 2-10 (Box-folder 36:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Jan 11-14 (Box-folder 36:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Jan 15-19 (Box-folder 36:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Jan 20-31 (Box-folder 36:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Feb 1-10 (Box-folder 36:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Feb 11-19 (Box-folder 36:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Feb 20-28 (Box-folder 36:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Mar 1-10 (Box-folder 36:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Mar 11-16 (Box-folder 36:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Mar 17-20 (Box-folder 36:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Mar 21-25 (Box-folder 36:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Mar 26-31 (Box-folder 36:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 April 1-10 (Box-folder 37:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 April 11-20 (Box-folder 37:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 April 21-30 (Box-folder 37:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 May 1-10 (Box-folder 37:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 May 11-16 (Box-folder 37:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 May 17-20 (Box-folder 37:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 May 21-25 (Box-folder 37:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 May 26-31 (Box-folder 37:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 June 1-12 (Box-folder 37:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 June 13-21, 22-31 (Box-folder 37:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 July 1-10 (Box-folder 38:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 July 11-24 (Box-folder 38:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 July 24-31 (Box-folder 38:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Aug 1-10 (Box-folder 38:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Aug 11-19 (Box-folder 38:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Sept 1-20 (Box-folder 38:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Sept 21-30 (Box-folder 38:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Oct 1-16 (Box-folder 38:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Oct 17-31 (Box-folder 38:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Nov 1-13 (Box-folder 38:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Nov 14-22 (Box-folder 38:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Nov 23-31 (Box-folder 38:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Dec 1-10 (Box-folder 38:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Dec 11-15 (Box-folder 38:14)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1941 Dec 16-31 (Box-folder 38:15)
    - Correspondence Congressional (Box-folder 39:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Jan 15-23 (Box-folder 39:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Jan 24-31 (Box-folder 39:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Feb 1-10 (Box-folder 39:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Feb 11-17 (Box-folder 39:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Feb 18-28 (Box-folder 39:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 March 1-15 (Box-folder 39:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 March 16-31 (Box-folder 39:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 April 1-15 (Box-folder 39:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 April 16-30 (Box-folder 39:10)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 May 1-15 (Box-folder 39:11)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 May 16-31 (Box-folder 39:12)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 June 1-15 (Box-folder 39:13)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 June 16-31 (Box-folder 39:14)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 July 1-4 (Box-folder 39:15)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 July 15-23 (Box-folder 39:16)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 July 1-15 (Box-folder 40:1)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 July 16-31 (Box-folder 40:2)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Aug 1-31 (Box-folder 40:3)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Sept 1-30 (Box-folder 40:4)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Oct 1-15 (Box-folder 40:5)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Oct 16-31 (Box-folder 40:6)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Nov 1-16 (Box-folder 40:7)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Nov 17-30 (Box-folder 40:8)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Dec 1-10 (Box-folder 40:9)
    - Correspondence Congressional 1942 Dec 11-31 (Box-folder 40:10)
- Correspondence Post Congressional
  - Post Congressional 1943 Jan (Box-folder 40:11)
  - Post Congressional 1943 Feb 1-15 (Box-folder 40:12)
  - Post Congressional 1943 Feb-May (Box-folder 40:13)
  - Post Congressional 1943 June-Aug (Box-folder 40:14)
  - Post Congressional 1943 Sept-Dec (Box-folder 40:15)
  - Post Congressional 1944 Jan-Feb (Box-folder 41:1)
  - Post Congressional 1944 Mar-Aug (Box-folder 41:2)
  - Post Congressional 1944 Sept-Dec (Box-folder 41:3)
  - Post Congressional 1945 Jan-July (Box-folder 41:4)
  - Post Congressional 1945 Sept-Dec (Box-folder 41:5)
  - Post Congressional 1946 Jan-June (Box-folder 41:6)
  - Post Congressional 1946 July-Dec (Box-folder 41:7)
  - Post Congressional 1947 (Box-folder 41:8)
  - Post Congressional 1948 (Box-folder 41:9)
  - Post Congressional 1949 (Box-folder 41:10)
  - Post Congressional 1950 (Box-folder 41:11)
  - Post Congressional 1951 (Box-folder 41:12)
  - Post Congressional 1952 (Box-folder 41:13)
  - Post Congressional 1953-1956 (Box-folder 41:14)
  - Post Congressional 1958,1968 (Box-folder 41:15)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:1)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:2)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:3)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:4)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:5)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:6)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:7)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:8)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:9)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:10)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:11)
  - Alph (Box-folder 42:12)
- The Mutual Housing Co.
  - Ledger 1921-1927 (Box-folder 43:1)
  - Ledger 1934 (Box-folder 43:2)
  - Ledger-Corporate Records (Box-folder 43:3)
  - Report-Mutual Housing Company 1925 (Box-folder 43:4)
  - Mutual Housing Co. Stock 1921 (Box-folder 44:1)
  - Mutual Housing Co. Minutes 1920-1923 (Box-folder 44:2)
  - Mutual Housing Co. Minutes 1924 (Box-folder 44:3)
  - Mutual Housing Co. Corporate Records 1920,1928 (Box-folder 44:4)
  - Mutual Housing Co. Financial Statement 1927-1930 (Box-folder 44:5)
  - Mutual Housing Co. Financial Statement 1928-1936 (Box-folder 44:6)
  - Mutual Housing Co. Financial statement 1936-1957 (Box-folder 44:7)
  - Mutual Housing Co. Financial statement 1925-1950 (Box-folder 44:8)
  - Mutual Housing Co. Financial statement 1924-1957 (Box-folder 44:9)
  - Mutual Housing Co. Financial statement 1956 (Box-folder 44:10)
- Mitchell v The United States
  - Initial Brief of Arthur W. Mitchell Complainant (I.C.C.) April 18, 1938 (Box-folder 44:11)
  - Arthur W. Mitchell v. The Illinois Central Railroad Company (I.C.C) April 20, 1938 (Box-folder 44:12)
  - Arthur W. Mitchell v. The Illinois Central Railroad (I.C.C.) May 24, 1938 (Box-folder 44:13)
  - Arthur Mitchell v. The United States of America (Box-folder 44:14)
  - The Supreme Court of the united States, arthur W. Mitchell v The Unitedf States Oct 1940 (Box-folder 44:15)
  - The Supreme Court of the united States, arthur W. Mitchell v The Unitedf States Oct 1940 (Box-folder 44:16)
  - The Supreme Court of the united States, arthur W. Mitchell v The Unitedf States Oct 1941 (Box-folder 44:17)
  - The Supreme Court of the united States, arthur W. Mitchell v The Unitedf States March 1941 (Box-folder 44:18)
  - The Supreme Court of the united States, arthur W. Mitchell v The Unitedf States June 1940 (Box-folder 44:19)
  - The Supreme Court of the united States, arthur W. Mitchell v The Illinois Central Railroad Company 1941 (Box-folder 44:20)
- Literary
  - Reports
    - The Treatment of the Negro Trainee 1943 (Box-folder 45:1)
    - The American Exposition 1940 (Box-folder 45:2)
    - "The Mob Still Rides", The Commision on Interracial Cooperation", "Negro Democracy" 1931-1935 (Box-folder 45:3)
  - Writing Articles
    - What has the New Deal Done for the Negro (Box-folder 45:4)
    - Congressman Mitchell takes on the NAACP (Box-folder 45:5)
    - The Negro and The National Preparedness Program 1940 (Box-folder 45:6)
    - No Title Jan 12, 1940 (Box-folder 45:7)
    - No Title Nov 1941 (Box-folder 45:8)
    - The Communist Party and The Negro in The United States (Box-folder 45:9)
    - Voting (Box-folder 45:10)
    - No Title (Box-folder 45:11)
    - No Title (Box-folder 45:12)
    - No Title (Box-folder 45:13)
    - Speeches In Home 1939-1940 (Box-folder 45:14)
    - Resolution- H.R E S 1935 (Box-folder 45:15)
    - Lynching in U.S. (Box-folder 45:16)
    - Black Resettlement April 24, 1939 (Box-folder 45:17)
    - Fourth District Correspondence (Box-folder 45:18)
    - Lynching states (Box-folder 45:19)
    - Negro Industrial Comm. Bill (Box-folder 45:20)
  - Speeches
    - Speeches Jan 9, 1938-1940 (Box-folder 45:21)
- Printed
  - Political Broadsides
    - Press Release- Resettlement (Box-folder 46:1)
    - Mitchell v R.I.R.R. (Box-folder 46:2)
    - R.I.R District Court 1938 (Box-folder 46:3)
    - Broadsides (originals) (Box-folder 46:4)
    - Publicity Report 1936 (Box-folder 46:5)
    - Tuskegee Messenger (Box-folder 46:6)
    - Broadside (copies) (Box-folder 46:7)
    - Political Broadsides (originals) (Box-folder 46:8)
    - Broadside (Dawson) (Box-folder 46:9)
    - The Tuskegee Messenger 1936 Mar-April (Box-folder 46:10)
    - Political Pamphlets (Box-folder 46:11)
    - Newsletters 1936 (Box-folder 46:12)
    - Bills House 1935 (Box-folder 46:13)
    - Roll Call Congress (Box-folder 46:14)
    - Congress Research 1935 (Box-folder 46:15)
  - News Clippings
    - The Evening Star 1935 (Box-folder 47:1)
    - Journal and Guide 1936 (Box-folder 47:2)
    - The Eagle 1935 (Box-folder 47:3)
    - Augusta Chronicle 1937 (Box-folder 47:4)
    - The Tuskegee Messenger 1934 (Box-folder 47:5)
    - Journal and Guide 1934 (Box-folder 47:6)
    - Chicago Bee 1940-1942 (Box-folder 47:7)
    - Seward Ward News (Box-folder 47:8)
    - The Chicago Daily News 1939-1941 (Box-folder 47:9)
    - Pittsburgh Courier 1934-1942 (Box-folder 47:10)
    - Midwest Daily Record 1938 (Box-folder 47:11)
    - The Franklin News Post 1937 (Box-folder 47:12)
    - Harrisburg Daily Register 1938 (Box-folder 47:13)
    - The Ashville Citizen 1937 (Box-folder 47:14)
    - The Northwest Enterprise 1937 (Box-folder 47:15)
    - Richmond Afro-American Planet 1947 (Box-folder 47:16)
    - The Voice 1938-1942 (Box-folder 47:17)
    - The St. Louis Argus 1935 (Box-folder 47:18)
    - Chicago Daily Tribune 1934-1936 (Box-folder 47:19)
    - The St. Louis Argus 1939-1941 (Box-folder 47:20)
    - Afro-American 1936 (Box-folder 47:21)
    - The Washington Afro-American 1937-42 (Box-folder 47:22)
    - The Washington Daily News 1935-1937 (Box-folder 47:23)
    - The Washington Post 1937-1941 (Box-folder 47:24)
    - Richmond Daily News 1947 (Box-folder 47:25)
    - Richmond Times Dispatch 1941 (Box-folder 47:26)
    - Normal School (West Ala) (Box-folder 47:27)
    - Afro-American 1935-1936 (Box-folder 47:28)
    - The Postal Alliance 1935-1940 (Box-folder 47:29)
    - The New York Age 1935-1937 (Box-folder 47:30)
    - The Montgomery Advertiser 1934-1941 (Box-folder 48:1)
    - New York Times 1937 (Box-folder 48:2)